我和我的兄弟姊妹
KLAUS: My siblings and I
是历史上最早的吸血鬼
are the first vampires
in all of history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
和他们不同的是，我是混合种
半吸血鬼半狼人
Unlike them, I am a Hybrid,
half vampire, half werewolf.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
Three hundred years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
现在我们回来了
被一群女巫引回来
Now, we've returned,
drawn back by a coven of witches
她们威胁着怀了我孩子的女人
who threatened the woman
carrying my child.
那个孩子会让我们都死去
That baby will bring
death to us all.
我哥哥以利亚和她们交涉过
KLAUS: My brother
Elijah dealt with them.
没人在伤害我的家人后能安然无恙
No one hurts
my family and lives.
我们以为海莉就会安全了
KLAUS: We thought Hayley
would be safe.
我是马赛尔
I'm Marcel.
我们好像没见过
I don't think we've met.
海莉不见了，她在哪？
Hayley is gone.
Where is she?
什么？
What?
马赛尔来过这里了
Marcel was here.
我们都错了
KLAUS: We were wrong.
女士们，先生们
Ladies, gentlemen...
欢迎来到决战之夜
...welcome to fight night!
决战之夜的第一条规则就是
And the first rule of fight night is,
今晚能够撑到最后的那个吸血鬼
the vampire left standing
at the end of the night
离进入我的亲信圈
is one step closer to the inner circle...
和这样的一枚日光戒指
and one of these...
就更近一步了
A daylight ring.
如果你们能用一点点的
极端暴力让我留下印象
If you can impress me
with a little ultra-violence,
同样也可以享受太阳照射在脸上的温暖
you too can enjoy the warmth
of the sun on your face.
你们所要做的，就是尽力决战
All you got to do
is kick a little ass.
开始吧
So, here we go.
首先出场的两位竞争者
Our first two contenders...
费莉西亚和奥托
...Felicia and Otto.
该死，妹子，不错嘛
Damn, girl, not bad.
晚安
Good evening.
我要说几句
I'd like a word.
你在干什么？
What do you think you're doing?
显然我们打断了
It appears that we've interrupted
一群脏兮兮的业余爱好者
a collection of filthy amateurs.
我们是为那个女孩来的
We've come here for the girl.
把她给我们，否则…
Give her to us, or...
我们就杀光这里所有人
...we kill everyone here.
从你开始
Starting with you.
你们俩真是太有勇气了
You two got a lot of nerve
居然来到我的地盘提要求
coming into my home
and making demands.
你的地盘，是吗？
You're home, is it?
那个女孩，我不会再说一次了
The girl.
I will not ask again.
我想你说的是海莉吧
I assume you're
talking about Hayley...
这么高，深色头发，态度傲慢
yay high, dark hair,
bitchy attitude.
对了，她是谁？
Who is she, anyway?
一位老朋友
She's an old friend.
你知道我对老朋友多有感情
You know how sentimental
I am about old friends.
她不在我手上
Well, I ain't got her,
在你们开始发牢骚之前
and before you start whining,
我承认今天晚上拜访过她
I did pay her a little visit
earlier tonight.
我感觉有点怀旧
I was feeling nostalgic.
所以我就去了种植园
So I took a trip out
to the plantation
我曾在那里做过奴隶
where I used to be a slave,
想像一下我有多惊讶
and imagine my surprise...
当我发现吸血鬼真祖家族
...when I realized that the
Original family of vampires
居然住在那里
had taken up residence.
你们的女孩海莉应了门
Your girl,Hayley, answered the door.
我们互相打了招呼，仅此而已
We exchanged hellos.
That was it.
你们不信就四处看看吧
You don't believe me,
look around.
我还会帮你们找她的
Hell, I'll even help you find her.
但我要问的是
But the question that I'd ask is...
如果海莉不在这里
If Hayley isn't here...
那她在哪？
...then where is she?
来真的啊？
Seriously?
泰勒？
Tyler?
你不会想跟我打的，海莉
你知道你没法打赢混合种
You don't want to fight me, Hayley.
You know you can't beat a Hybrid.
放开我
Let me go,
你这个卑鄙的混血杂…
you backstabbing,
half-breed piece of sh--
闭嘴！
Shut up!
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：血腥杀戮
并不是很招人喜欢的群体，不是吗？
ELlJAH: Not the most
attractive community, are they?
你知道他们能听见你说话
You do realize they can hear you.
你知道我不在乎
You do realize I don't care.
以利亚
主演：约瑟夫摩根
You know, Elijah,
我更喜欢你待在棺材里
I liked you better in that box,
但是克劳斯，我的父亲
我对你无限感激
but, Klaus, my sire,
you I owe the world...
而且我向来尊重长辈
...and I always show respect
to my elders.
如果你们特别的女性朋友失踪了
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
If your special
lady friend is missing,
你们可以找个女巫帮你们
主演：克莱儿荷特
you can benefit
from the help of a witch,
既然我控制着城里的所有女巫
and since I control
all the witches in this town,
我允许你们使用一个小小的定位咒
I'll grant you one little locator spell.
莎宾是法语区最好的导游
主演：菲比托金
Sabine is the best guide
in the Quarter.
如果你们要找人
You need to find someone,
我保证她可以帮上忙
I guarantee she's your girl.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
我真的很想继续聊
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
但太阳就快要升起了
I hate to cut this short,
but the sun is coming up soon.
我的夜行者们得回到屋内
My nightwalkers
need to get inside,
而我还有一个城市要管理
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
and I've got a city to run.
你们就自己寻找你们的迷途羔羊吧
I'll leave you to track down
your lost sheep.
你能找到她吗？
Can you find her?
可以试试
I can try.
主演：莉雅派普斯
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
路易斯安那的一处
The armpit of Louisiana.
你拿那个做什么？
What are you gonna do with that?
这就看你了
Depends on you.
嘿，是你攻击我的，记得吗？
Hey, you attacked me, remember?
你在我家后院埋伏我
You ambushed me
in my own back yard.
那不是你家后院，是克劳斯的
It's not your back yard.
It's Klaus'.
你只是和那个疯子住在那个房子里
You're shacked up in a mansion
with that psycho,
和我在阿帕拉契山脉认识的
a long way from the girl
I met in the Appalachians
帮助其他狼人的女孩完全两样
helping other werewolves.
泰勒，对不起
但自从我最后一次见你之后
Tyler, I'm sorry,
but a lot has happened
发生了许多事
since the last time I saw you.
比如你是如何怀孕的吗？
You mean like
how you're pregnant?
混合种婴儿，是的，我都知道了
A Hybrid baby. Yeah.
I know all about it.
我一直在河口
I've been roaming
四处打探
around the bayou asking questions.
我来告诉你我打听到了什么
Let me tell you what I learned.
这个新月胎记意味着你来自
This crescent birthmark
means you come
一个重要的家族
算是这个地区
from a big shot family,
some kind of royalty
狼人的皇族
to the werewolves
of this region,
就是这里
制片：兰斯安德森
and right here...
这就是他们仅剩的了
This is all that's left of them.
嘿，帮帮我
Hey, help me.
他们帮不了你
They can't help you.
他们躲藏在树林里
They're in the woods hiding
因为他们被吸血鬼迫害了数十年
because they've been persecuted
for decades by vampires.
是她吗？
Is that her?
是的，杜恩
带她进去
Yeah, Dwayne.
Get her inside.
泰勒？泰勒？
Tyler? Tyler?
她在很偏远的地方
She's in the back country.
在霍玛一带，河口深处
Way out past Houma,
deep in the bayou.
我也不指望你能说得更具体
I don't suppose
you could be more precise.
怎么了，以利亚？
What's the matter, Elijah?
你担心沼泽溅起的泥水
Are you worried a bit of
splashing about in the bog
会毁掉你昂贵的鞋子吗？
might ruin
your expensive shoes?
事实上，在经历了最近的囚禁之后
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
As a matter of fact,
after my recent confinement,
我可以优雅地穿过乡野
I could use a decent stroll
through the countryside.
那里有被驱逐的狼人的传说
There are stories of exiled werewolves.
他们的营地
Encampments.
如果海莉真去了那么远
很有可能她是去找他们了
If Hayley went out that far,
chances are, she went to find them.
显然她希望结交更多同种族的人
Clearly, she hopes to make the
acquaintance of more like herself.
我想我们的陪伴可能不够好呢
I suppose our company
wasn't good enough for her.
编剧：麦可鲁梭
麦克纳度奇
你可以随时加入他们的
导演：杰弗利亨特
You could always join them, you know.
喝酒游戏
Ah, drinking games.
我不是很喜欢
It's not really my thing.
有点让我想起中学时的那些运动员
It kind of reminds me of the jocks
in my high school.
我们学校有很多你们说的
We had a pretty high quota
of what you'd call
混帐东西
douche nozzles.
- 恶霸啊？
- 是啊
-Bullies, huh?
-Yeah.
很好奇如果你现在看到那些家伙会怎样
Wonder what'd happen if
you saw those guys now.
我敢说你一定会撕碎他们的，对吧？
I bet you'd tear them apart, right?
是啊，当然
Yeah, totally.
可能会把所有吸血鬼的招数
都用在他们身上
Probably go all vamp ninja on 'em.
你是个有趣的家伙，小约
You're a funny guy, Josh.
事实上，我觉得昨晚真的很有趣
你知道吗？
In fact, I thought it was really
funny last night, you know?
看到你在克劳斯住的那个种植园里
Seeing you at that plantation
where Klaus is staying.
你要去什么地方吗，小约？
You going somewhere, Josh?
我们应该朝南向水边走
We should head south
towards the water.
你似乎下定决心要找到那只小狼
You seem quite determined
to find the little wolf.
如果你觉得我走太快了，尼克劳斯
If I'm moving too fast for you, Niklaus,
你可以去车里等着
you're welcome to wait in the car.
不过要保证不许把窗户摇上
Do be certain to leave
the windows down.
我碰到你的痛处了吧
So, I've touched a nerve.
你开始欣赏这个女孩了
You've begun to admire this girl.
也许这就是为什么你一回来就开始
Perhaps that's why
you've been barking orders
厉声下命今
希望透过扮演家长的角色
since your return,
hoping to impress Hayley
让海莉留下好印象
by assuming the role of family patriarch.
如果你想坚持把她当作活动的孵卵器
You want to insist on treating her
like a walking incubator,
那就是你的错
then that's your mistake.
你发现她的气味了吗？
Have you found her scent?
没有
No.
但我发现其他人的了
But I found someone else's.
这辆车散发着某个
This vehicle reeks...
我以为除掉的人的臭味
...of someone I thought
I was rid of....
泰勒洛克伍
Tyler Lockwood.
为什么你迷瀑镇的混合种小跟班
And why would your
little Hybrid sidekick from Mystic Falls
对海莉有兴趣呢？
have any interest in Hayley?
他想要复仇，因为我追求了他的女朋友
He wants revenge
because I went after his girl.
为什么我怀疑这又是你的错呢？
Why do I suspect this
is the least of your offenses?
在我还有办法转变混合种时
Back when I had the means
to sire Hybrids,
他是我的第一个
he was my first.
尽管在这件事上我没给他多少选择
Although I didn't give him
much choice in the matter.
一开始他很忠诚
He was loyal in the beginning,
但慢慢就开始不听话了
but he grew insubordinate.
还让我其他的混合种都与我作对
Turned my other Hybrids
against me.
我无法容忍
I couldn't have that.
所以我就杀了很多混合种
So, I massacred
the lot of them.
在我了结泰勒之前
Tyler ran like a coward
他就像个懦夫一样逃走了
before I could finish him off.
你还有什么要说的吗？
Anything else that
you would like to share?
还有和他妈妈有关的事情
Well, there was
this business with his mum.
你杀了他母亲，好极了
You killed his mother.
Wonderful.
他应该得到教训
He needed to be taught a lesson.
你又该得到什么教训呢，尼克劳斯
And what lesson will
you be taught, Niklaus,
如果他透过伤害海莉来报复？
if he retaliates by harming Hayley?
所以你的确是在乎她的
So you do care about her.
那就去啊
Well, go on, then.
去吧，哥哥，去救她
Have at it, brother.
Save her.
索求你的战利品
她的一切我都尝过了
Claim what spoils you can.
I've sampled what she has to offer,
让我告诉你，她可是妙不可言呢
and, let me tell you,
she is exquisite.
尼克劳斯，帮帮我…
Niklaus, so help me--
够了
Enough.
我会亲手杀了泰勒洛克伍
I'll kill
Tyler Lockwood myself.
马赛尔，有情况
Marcel, something is happening.
法语区有女巫在施魔法
There's a witch doing
magic in the Quarter.
别担心，那是我批准的
Oh, no worries.
That one is Marcel-approved.
除此之外…
Besides...
还有别的东西需要你处理
(JOSH GROANS)
I got something else
for you to handle.
不，你就是那个超级女巫
Oh, no.
You're the super witch.
和小约打个招呼吧
Say hi to Josh.
你为什么把他带来这里？
Why would you bring him here?
小约有个问题
Josh has a problem.
克劳斯魅惑他监视我
Klaus compelled him
to spy on me.
我不能容忍
I can't have that.
所以我就想“我要杀了小约”
So I thought,
"I'll just kill Josh."
马赛尔，求求你，这不是我的错
Marcel, please.
It's not my fault.
然后我又想“杀死一个吸血鬼
Then I thought,
"Killing a vampire,
会坏了我自己的规矩”
that would be breaking
my own rule."
聪明的做法就是让他回到我这边来
Smart thing to do is to flip Josh.
那样他就可以告诉把我想说的
告诉克劳斯
That way, he can tell Klaus
whatever I want.
甚至可以替我监视他
He could even spy for me.
我们只要抹去克劳斯对他的魅惑
All we got to do
is wipe away that compulsion.
你觉得怎么样？
So, what do you think?
我可以让他忘记克劳斯跟他说的话
I can make him forget
what Klaus told him,
但克劳斯说得越多
but the more Klaus said,
就会越痛
the more it's gonna hurt.
可能会非常痛呢
Probably gonna hurt a lot.
小约？
Josh?
我可以
I'll do it.
做什么都可以
Anything, yes.
到底有多痛？
How much pain are we talking?
泰勒，最近一直有只狼看护着我
Tyler, there has been a wolf,
watching me lately.
保护着我，就好像他本能地知道
我是他一族的
Protecting me like it instinctively
knows that I am part of its pack.
你是混合种
你可以随时变成狼
You're a Hybrid. You can turn into
a wolf whenever you want.
是你吗？
Was it you?
不是，但你说得对
No.
But you're right.
只有混合种才能控制自己何时变身
Only Hybrids can control,
when they change.
而我是除了克劳斯之外唯一的混合种
And I'm the only one left
besides Klaus.
所以我们才在这里
Which is why we're here.
不管你以为自己在做什么
Whatever you think you're doing,
你知道真祖家族都…
you know that
whole Original family
订下了约定什么的
has made some sort of
pact or something
确保我和孩子的安全
to keep me and the baby safe.
如果你伤害我，他们会杀了你的
So, if you hurt me,
they'll kill you.
你凭什么觉得我怕死？
What makes you think
I'm afraid to die?
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready for this?
动手吧
Let's do it.
你们要干什么？
What are you doing?
泰勒，拜托，不要，泰勒
Tyler, please.
No. Tyler!
克劳斯毁了我生命中所有美好的事情
Klaus destroyed everything
good in my life.
所以我就要夺走他最想要的东西
So I'm gonna take away
the thing he wants most.
不要，拜托，泰勒，求求你
No, please! Tyler, please!
我以为你离开了
没法袖手旁观，是吗？
I thought you were leaving town.
Couldn't stay away, huh?
我已经穿过半个路易斯安那州
才发现你入侵了我家
I was half past Louisiana when
I found out you invaded our home.
你对海莉做了什么？
What have you done
with Hayley?
你生气的时候真性感
You're so hot when you're angry.
你利用了我
You used me!
我确定那是相互的
I'm pretty sure that was mutual.
被你的魅力所骗
我像傻瓜一样和你睡了
Beguiled by your charms,
I slept with you like a fool,
把你带去了我家，然后你就带走了海莉
Ied you to our home,
and then you took Hayley.
我没有带走任何人
Whoa, I didn't take anybody.
我已经和你哥哥们澄清这件事了
I already sorted this out
with your brothers.
别回避问题
But it begs the question...
你为什么回来？
...why'd you come back?
如果克劳斯知道你找到
If Klaus learns it's my fault
种植园是因为我…
you found your way
to the plantation--
你真觉得我会出卖你吗？
You really think I'd rat you out?
行了吧
Come on.
如果你觉得我在一千年里
If you think that
I'd ever in 1,000 years
会做出什么事伤害你
do anything to hurt you,
你就是错把我当作克劳斯了
you got me confused with Klaus.
你的魅力和挑逗
All your charms and flirtations...
足够证明你就是和克劳斯一样的
...simply prove you're every bit the liar
骗子和操控者
and manipulator that Klaus is,
你真的这么想吗？
Is that what you really think?
请一定要证明我错了
By all means, prove me wrong.
好吧，跟我来
Fine. Come on.
有样东西要给你看
Something you need to see.
别想批判我
Don't get all judge-y.
杜恩知道自己卷入了何事
Dwayne knew what he was getting into.
他是自愿的
He volunteered.
让你杀了他吗？
For you to kill him?
杜恩是狼人，死时身体里有你的血
Dwayne is a werewolf who died
with your blood in his system,
你和你的混合种宝宝共有的血
same blood you share
with your Hybrid baby.
你想把他变成混合种
那是不可能的
You're trying to turn him into a Hybrid.
That's impossible.
和这一带的狼群都交流过后
Been running with wolf packs
all over the country.
其中有一个和一个女巫关系很不错
One of them was tight
with a witch.
她噩梦中有你孩子的幻象
She had nightmare visions
about your baby
以及克劳斯如何利用它的血
来建造一支混合种奴隶军队
and how Klaus could use its blood
to make an army of Hybrid slaves.
我受够了这些女巫
I am sick of these witches
还有关于我孩子的预言
and the premonitions
about my baby.
这只是个孩子
It's just a baby.
也许是，也许不是
Maybe. Maybe not.
所以杜恩才会来
That's where Dwayne comes in.
你看，他很乐意做试验品
You see, he was happy
to be the test case.
你还没有注意到吧
这些人的生活没什么指望
If you haven't noticed,
these people don't have much to live for.
他们很乐意接受成为
They'd all welcome the chance
上等物种的机会
to become the superior species.
问题是，所有混合种都是克劳斯转变的
Trouble is,
all Hybrids are sired to Klaus.
他们对他言听计从
They follow his every move.
我不可能让这一切发生的
No way I'd let that happen.
你怎么就这么确定克劳斯知道
How can you be
so sure Klaus knows
这孩子的血能做什么？
what the baby's blood will do?
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
克劳斯米卡森
Klaus Mikaelson,
男人、女人、小狗的杀手
killer of men, women, and puppies,
突然之间想要做爸爸了？
all of a sudden
wants to be a daddy?
或者说他根本就别有用心
Or he's got an ulterior motive.
混合种可以在阳光下行走
Hybrids can walk in the sun.
他们咬一口就可以让吸血鬼死亡
Their bite is lethal to vampires.
一周时间他们就能接管纽奥良
They'll take over New Orleans
by the end of the week,
你知道那时什么才能阻止克劳斯吗？
and you know what's
gonna stop Klaus then?
什么都阻止不了
Nothing.
你得吸她的血
You're gonna have to feed on her.
什么？不要
What? No.
快点
Do it.
杜恩，放轻松
Dwayne?
Easy.
看着我
Look at me.
Look at me!
你没事了
You're okay.
我好得很
I'm better than okay.
抱歉，但这样只会更糟
I'm sorry,
but it's just gonna get worse.
克劳斯的魅惑太深了
Klaus' compulsion runs deep.
你得想想其他事情
You need to think of something else.
尽量不去想这个
Take your mind off it.
你喜欢音乐吗？
Do you like music?
什么？什么？
What? Wha--?
我现在没法想音乐
I can't think
about music right now.
为什么？我不知道
Why? I don't know.
也许是因为你给我施了巫毒脑叶切除术
Maybe because you're
giving me a voodoo lobotomy.
你喜欢爵士乐吗？
Do you like jazz?
那你喜欢什么？
So what, then?
夜店那种
Club stuff.
浩室舞曲、出神舞曲，你懂的
House, trance, you know....
我是女巫，不是阿米希人
I'm a witch.
I'm not Amish.
我才16岁，我不去夜店
It's just I'm only 16.
I don't go to clubs.
我16岁时都去过上百家夜店了
When I was 16,
I'd been to, like, a hundred clubs.
天哪，这才是四年前
God, it was only four years ago.
感觉却像是上辈子
Feels like another life.
我当时只想认识新朋友
All I wanted to do was meet boys.
事情却变得非常复杂
Things are so much more complicated.
现在我只想认识新朋友
I mean, now all I want
to do is meet boys
吸人类的血
and feed
on people's blood...
得到一枚日光戒指
Get one of those daylight rings
这样我就不会被阳光灼伤
so I don't burn in the sunlight.
都是些再正常不过的东西了
All perfectly normal things.
我喜欢古典乐
I like the classics.
普契尼、巴哈、莫札特
Puccini, Bach, Mozart.
我学过钢琴
I took piano.
不过被困在这后也没什么意义了
Not that it matters
while I'm stuck here.
为什么？
Why not?
马赛尔担心会有人听到琴声
Marcel is worried
that someone could hear.
这不是他的错
It's not his fault.
他只是想保护我
He just wants to keep me safe.
保护你什么？
Safe from what?
简单来说，就是一群疯婆子女巫
Basically, a coven of psycho witches
想让我在一场血祭上当祭品
want to sacrifice me
in a blood ritual.
原来是这样，好吧
Oh, wow. Okay.
我很…遗憾？
Uh, I'm sorry?
没关孙，我会将她们全部消灭
Don't be.
I'm gonna destroy them all.
一旦她们不复存在
And once they're gone,
一切将会恢复正常
everything will go back to normal.
我也能过回原来的生活
I'll have my old life back.
成功了，是吗？
他成为混合种了
It worked, didn't it?
He's a Hybrid.
如果你落到克劳斯手里
If Klaus gets a hold of you,
如果他控制了那个孩子，他就赢了
if he gets that kid, he wins.
那就帮我把孩子藏起来
Then help me hide the baby from him.
帮助我逃跑
Help me run.
他会找到你的
He'll find you.
他会夺走你的孩子
He'll take your kid away,
然后制造更多凶残的混合种
and he'll make
more Hybrid monsters.
服从他一切命令的奴隶
Slaves who do everything he says.
泰勒，无论你想做什么
Tyler, whatever you're
thinking of doing,
总会有另一种方法的
there has to be another way.
你不是这样的人
You're not like this.
这么做太愚蠢了
That was stupid.
离她远点
Get away from her.
- 你管得着吗？
- 我说，离她远点
-What do you care?
-I said, get away.
你已经如愿以偿了，快滚
You got what you wanted.
Now get lost.
杜恩，他想杀了我
Dwayne, he's gonna kill me.
他也想杀了你
And he's gonna kill you, too.
他说混合种存在这世上太危险了
He said that Hybrids
are too dangerous to live.
你一定要阻止他
You need to stop him.
你给我闭嘴
Shut up!
抱歉
Forgive me.
我还以为你有危险
Thought you were in danger.
看来是我想错了
It appears I was mistaken.
你绝对想不到我今天过得有多糟
You will not believe the crap day
that I'm having.
我带你回家
Let me take you home.
以利亚
Elijah?
关于孩子，有些事情我想告诉你
There's something you need
to know about the baby.
海莉
Hayley?
别让事情变得更复杂
Don't make this harder
than it has to be.
放弃抵抗吧
Give up now.
我会给你个痛快的
I'll end it quick.
真是不错的提议
KLAUS: Quite an offer.
但我可就不会这样对你了
Though not one
I'll be extending to you.
克劳斯
Klaus.
你好，泰勒
你气色不错
Hello, Tyler.
You look well.
不过我打算改变一下
I aim to change that.
为了报复我
Threatening a pregnant girl
你居然威胁一个孕妇
in order to exact
revenge against me.
我从没想过你会变得如此不堪
I never expected you
to sink so low.
不得不承认，我对你刮目相看
I admit, I'm impressed.
我以前也跟你混了不少日子
I used to hang out with you.
或多或少也学到了一点
I guess something
must have rubbed off.
如果卡洛琳知道你变成这样
What do you think
Caroline would say
不知道她会怎么想呢？
if she saw what you've become?
或许当我在电话里告诉她你的死讯时
Perhaps I'll ask her
when I call her
我会亲自问问她
to tell her of your demise.
无论我变成怎样
Whatever happens to me,
也不会消除卡洛琳对你的恨意
Caroline is never
gonna stop hating you.
来吧，兄弟，尽你所能
Come on, mate.
Give it a bit more effort.
我想好好享受这一刻
I wanna enjoy myself.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
这是花园
This is the garden.
是我用来惩罚那些
违反我规矩的吸血鬼的地方
It's where I punish vampires
who break my rules.
但很久以前，这里本来不是这样的用途
But a long time ago,
used to be something else.
来，告诉我你看到了什么
Go on.
Tell me what you see.
两层楼、希腊圆柱
Two stories,
Greek columns,
环烧式门廊、挑高天花板
wrap-around porch,
high ceilings,
还有气窗
transom windows.
很漂亮的房子，那又怎样？
It's lovely.
So what?
是我为你设计的，原本是我们的房子
So, I designed it for you.
It was gonna be ours.
那个
That....
这里本该是我们俩的幸福结局吗？
This was supposed to be
our happily ever after?
是的，属于你和我
Yours and mine.
只是你跟克劳斯离开了这里
Except you flew the coop
with Klaus.
当时这里已经打好了地基
I already built
the foundation for the place.
在你走后，我中止了工程
I halted construction after you took off.
本想等你回来后继续的
Plan was to wait for you to return.
但你再也没回来
You never did.
所以现在这里被用来埋葬背叛我的人
So, now it's where I bury
the people who betray me.
你可以去找我啊
You could've come after me.
你和克劳斯在一起，我不知道你在哪
You were with Klaus.
I didn't know where.
我不知道你是否还想和我在一起
I didn't know if you
still wanted to be with me.
你只要回家就会找到我
All you had to do was come home.
事情没那么简单
It was more complicated than that.
我们离开不久
Not long after we left here,
他就给我插了匕首
he put a dagger in my heart
然后把我锁在棺材里90年
and stuck me in a box
for 90 years.
他整整偷走了我一个世纪的时间
He stole a century from me
like it were nothing.
这就是他的为人，蕾贝卡
That's what he does, Rebekah.
克劳斯永远不会满足
Klaus will never be happy.
他得不到的东西永远也不会
He'll be damned
if he lets anyone get something
- 让别人得到
- 我知道
-that he can't have.
-I know.
我已经按照他的指示活了一千年
I've been dancing to this song
for a thousand years.
从现在起，你有个选择
Starting right now,
you have a choice...
一个是随心所欲，任意夺走
...between the brother who
takes away your happiness
你幸福的哥哥
另一个是
whenever he feels like it
and the man who wants
想满足你任何需求的男人
to give you everything
you ever wanted.
为了泄恨
他会当着我的面杀掉你
He will kill you in front of my eyes
out of spite.
如果我们先摆脱他就不会了
Not if we get rid of him first.
克劳斯一定已经知道了
Klaus must have known.
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation.
他对宝宝不闻不问
He could care less
about the baby.
只是想要她出生
He just wants her to be born
这样他就能利用她制造更多混合种
so he can use her
to make more sired Hybrids.
虽然杜恩的表现
Although the way
that Dwayne was acting,
更像是被我转变的
it was more like
he was sired to me.
我应该带你回家
I should take you home.
你是认真的吗？哪里还有家？
Are you serious?
Home to what?
听着，不管我弟弟的意图如何
我还是保持本意
Look. Regardless of my brother's
intentions, mine remain the same.
我说过会保护你
I said that I would protect you,
就算是克劳斯想伤害你也不行
even, if need be,
from Klaus himself.
我可以照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
一直以来都是这样的
I've done it for a long time.
这就是你的复仇计划吗，泰勒？
Is this your idea of revenge, Tyler?
累人的捉迷藏游戏？
Grueling game of hide-and-seek?
啊！
Aah!
让我们结束这一切吧，怎么样？
Let's end this, shall we?
胆子不小啊你
How dare you?
这才是开始
I'm just getting started.
你变得残忍了
You've grown bloodthirsty.
也许你该庆幸你母亲没有活着
Perhaps it's best
your mother didn't live
看到你这个样子
to see you like this.
真是难过
It's sad, really.
我以为自己把你塑造得很好
I thought I made you better.
结果你这么的令人失望
Turns out,
you're quite the disappointment.
我想我是你另一个失败的例子
I guess I'm another one
of your failures.
就像你没有成功制造出混合种
Like how you failed
at making Hybrids,
搞得家族四分五裂
how you failed your family.
现在看来你又要失去自己的孩子了
Now it looks like
you're even gonna fail your own kid.
然后就这样结束你无趣的小命吧
And thus ends
your tedious little life.
至少不会耗时太久
At least it was brief.
做啊
Do it.
你永远不可能撕碎我
You're never gonna break me.
唯一能做的就是杀了我
Only thing you could do is kill me.
来吧，继续啊，快点结束一切
So go on. Go on.
Get it over with!
你想让我结束你的痛苦，是吗？
You want me to end your suffering,
don't you, hmm?
我确实是让你支离破碎
夺走了你的一切
I did break you,
took everything from you,
现在你又乞求我清理干净
and now you're begging me
to sweep away the shards
你那破碎卑微的生命
of your shattered, little life.
让你死就太便宜你了
Death offers more peace
than you deserve.
让你活着岂不是更好
It's better to let you live,
每天早上你一醒来就会意识到
and each morning,
you will wake knowing
自己能继续悲惨地活着
that your wretched
existence continues
是因为我的意愿
only by my will.
现在滚，并且在你剩下的日子里
Now go and live
the rest of your days
记住你对我来说一文不值
knowing you are nothing to me.
你知道有多少傻子
Do you know how many
fools have tried
尝试击败我哥哥吗？
to vanquish my brother?
如果你反抗他，他就杀掉你
If you stand against him,
he will kill you,
那种可怕又血腥的场面
and it will be awful and bloody,
我可不想在一旁欣赏
and I will not stand around
and watch.
你忘了我有秘密武器
You forget I have a secret weapon.
黛维娜，几世纪以来最厉害的女巫
Davina, the most powerful witch
in the last couple centuries.
如果她能找到杀掉他的方法呢
What if she can find a way to kill him?
你还是不明白，对吧？
You don't know, do you?
你杀了克劳斯的话
You can't kill Klaus,
自己也会跟着死
not without dying yourself.
我哥哥柯尔和芬恩的死教给我们
We learned it from the deaths
of my brothers Kol and Finn.
如果一个真祖死掉，那他们这条
If an Original dies,
血脉的吸血鬼都会跟着死去
every vampire ever made from their line
dies with him.
即使你杀掉克劳斯，他还是赢家
Even if you kill Klaus,
he'll still win.
一千年来都是这样
It's been that way
for a thousand years.
这就是他的手段，他永远都是赢家
That's his trick.
He always wins.
还有一个方法
There's another way.
什么方法？
What would that be?
- 我们把他永远埋葬于此
- 你疯了吗？
-We bury him down here forever.
-Are you mad?
你这惊骇小密室也许能关得住
This little chamber
of horrors may work
你那帮乌合之众
但你真的认为
for your riffraff,
but do you really think
这能关住我哥哥吗？
it will hold my brother?
难道不值得冒这个险吗？
Isn't it worth the risk?
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right.
克劳斯永远不会停止控制你
Klaus will never stop trying
to control you.
难道我就该相信
And I'm supposed to believe that...
在一个世纪后，你突然心甘情愿
after a century, suddenly you're willing
冒着死在他手上的危险
也要和我在一起吗？
to risk death
at his hands to be with me?
我想捍卫我的家园
I want to defend my home.
我想要自由
I want to be free,
如果这也意味着我能和你在一起
and if that means
I get to be with you,
就更有理由要把他埋在这了
all the more reason to bury him.
现在告诉我，你想要什么？
Now you tell me,
what do you want?
你们总算来了
There you are.
看来你找到我们迷途的羔羊了
I see you found our wandering stray.
也许她能给我
Perhaps she could
解释一下情况
shed some light on the situation.
这个
This...
显然是具混合种尸体
...would appear to be
the body of a Hybrid.
他叫杜恩
His name was Dwayne.
不管他是谁，不是我转变的
Well, whoever he was,
I didn't sire him.
知道这是怎么一回事吗？
Any idea how that's possible?
说得好像你真不知道一样
As if you didn't know.
你们俩倒成了好朋友了
Aren't you two fast friends?
快说吧
Well, come on, then.
你们共谋了什么可怕的罪名
What horrible accusation
have you conspired
要安在我头上？
to levy against me?
泰勒洛克伍带海莉来
是为了验证一个雅测
Tyler Lockwood brought Hayley
here to test a theory.
她孩子的血液能创造混合种
That the blood of her child
could be used to sire Hybrids.
他声称你早就知道这事
He claims you knew that.
更有甚者，你打算利用这点建立军队
Furthermore, you intended to use
this knowledge to build an army.
显然你也认为这是真的
And, of course,
you assume it's true.
不然我怎么会
I mean, why else would I show
对自己的亲生骨肉有任何的兴趣？
any interest in my
own flesh and blood?
一个悲痛欲绝的爱哭小鬼
A heartbroken, little crybaby
points his finger at me,
公然指控我，而我的亲哥哥
却深信不疑，巴不得全盘接受
and my own brother falls in line,
eager to believe it.
你总能快速得出最坏的预测
How quickly you assume the worst...
尤其是当这出自她口中时
Especially when it comes from her.
少装出一副愤慨的样子
ELlJAH:
Spare me your indignation.
你什么时候对海莉和她的孩子
When have you ever demonstrated
any kind of concern
展露过任何关心
towards Hayley or her child
除非是为了你的一己之私
beyond your own selfish pursuits?
你曾经还对我说过什么？
And what was it
you once said to me?
“每个国王都要有继承者”
"Every king needs an heir."
我的好哥哥
My big brother...
所以说你怀疑我的意图
So, you doubt my intentions.
倒不能说是意料之外
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
与高尚的以利亚相比
Standing beside the noble Elijah,
无论如何我都是不成器的弟弟
how can I be anything
but the lesser brother?
一个骗子、一个操纵者
A liar, a manipulator...
一个杂种？
A bastard?
对你来说，我不过如此，对吧？
That's all I am to you, isn't it?
蕾贝卡亦然
And to Rebekah.
而且由海莉对你言听计从的样子看来
And judging by the way Hayley
hangs on your every word,
显然她也是这么想的
it's clear she feels the same way.
毫无疑问我的孩子有朝一日也会如此
No doubt, my child will,
as well.
弟弟，如果我…
Brother, if l--
该说的我们都已经说完了
哥哥
We have said
all that needs to be said, brother.
我会好好扮演被赋予的角色
I'll play the role I've been given.
你们俩好好相依作伴吧
You two enjoy each other's company.
幻觉和痴呆的症状一旦发作
You'll have much to bond over,
你们就更相依为命了
once the hallucinations
and dementia set in.
这一口就当作是
Consider that bite
我送给你们的离别礼物吧
my parting gift to you both.
结束了
That's it.
你自由了
You're free.
你说得没错，我能感觉到
You're right.
I can feel it.
之前我总是想着
Before, I was always thinking about
克劳斯会想要我做什么
what Klaus would want me to do.
现在我想的是“去他的
Now I'm, like,
"Screw that guy."
克劳斯米卡森吃屎去吧
Klaus Mikaelson can suck it.
怎么了？怎么这副表情？
What?
What's that look for?
马赛尔要我让你忘了我
Marcel wants me to make you
forget about me.
哦，你不需要这么做
Oh, well,
you don't have to do that.
我的命是你救的
I, like, owe you my life.
我会替你保密的
I'll keep your secret.
再说，能再次和正常人
Besides, it's kind of nice
聊聊天还蛮不错的
just talking to someone normal again.
你觉得我正常吗？
You think I'm normal?
我是个像怪胎一样隐居在教堂阁楼的
I'm a 16-year-old witch
living in a church attic
16岁女巫
Iike some kind of freak.
我是个喜欢混夜店的男同志
I'm a gay club kid who died
死过一次又复活成吸血鬼
and came back as a vampire.
是啊
Yeah.
正常是相对而言的，对吧？
Normal is kind of relative,
you know?
来，我们打勾勾发誓
Here.
Pinky swear on it.
你不必帮我
You don't have to help.
我能自己翻找这堆狼人古董
I can dig through
the werewolf antique show on my own.
还有，你不用涂点药膏
Besides, shouldn't
you put some kind
或什么的在伤口上吗？
of ointment or
something on that?
那咬伤杀不了我
The bite won't kill me.
这咬伤就像尼克劳斯一样
Like Niklaus himself,
it's more of a nuisance
顶多算是个无法赶走的麻烦
than anything, really.
好吧，反正我也需要
Good, because I'm eventually
有人送我回家
gonna need a ride home.
另外，感谢你在这里守着
And thanks, by the way,
for staying out here.
你不必那样做的
You didn't have to.
我知道
I know.
但你说这个村子的人
But you said the people
of this village
是你所有的家人了
are all of the family
you have left.
我能感同身受
I can relate.
你在想克劳斯
You're thinking about Klaus.
也许是我太想给他扣上罪名了
Perhaps I was too willing
to condemn him.
在我们一起的这一千年里
In the 1,000 years
that we have been together,
我弟弟犯下了许多令人发指的罪行
my brother has committed
numerous unspeakable acts,
但蕾贝卡也是
but, then again, so has Rebekah.
还有我也是
So have l.
我上次在卡布的时候也是
So did I the last time I was in Cabo.
我们都做过坏事
We all do bad things.
只是大多数人
It's just, most people die
都在罪行过多之前就死了
before the list gets embarrassing.
但你绝不要拿自己和克劳斯比
But don't for a second
compare yourself to Klaus.
这里就像个蒸笼一样
It's like a freaking hotbox in here.
我要出去透透气
I'm gonna get some air.
有人把这个留在这里了
Someone left this here.
这是什么？
What is it?
一本印有
A Bible... with a family tree
家族族谱的圣经
that goes back generations.
这些人是谁？
What are these names?
安德莉亚是谁？
Who is Andrea?
我想是我
I think I am.
那是我出生的日子
That's the day that I was born.
我以为你离开了
I thought you were leaving us.
我们都清楚这个家
We both know this family
不能没有我
can barely function without me.
以利亚和海莉在哪？
Where are Elijah and Hayley?
我把他们留在河口了
I left them in the bayou.
为什么？
Why?
我和以利亚起了点小争执
Elijah and I had a bit of a row.
海莉怂恿他与我作对
Hayley has conspired
to turn him against me.
你也知道我们哥哥从来就
And you know our brother
never was one
过不了美人关
to resist a pretty face.
种种阴错阳差下，我咬了他
So one thing led to another,
and I bit him.
把他们两个都留在那里了
Left them both
stranded in the swamp.
插匕首、咬伤、抛弃
Daggering, biting, deserting.
你的这些恶行都没有尽头吗？
Does your wickedness ever end?
我的这些恶行都是为了自保
My wickedness
is self-preservation,
如果不是因为在各方面
and I wouldn't have
to go to such lengths
我都被陷于不义
were I not beset on all sides
我也不会做那些事
by incompetence and treachery.
既然以利亚抛弃了我
Now that Elijah
has abandoned me,
我需要你帮助我对抗马赛尔
I'll be needing you
in my plot against Marcel.
别太着急想着离开这里
Don't expect to be
leaving town any time soon.
你这么对以利亚，我为什么要帮你？
Why should I help you
after what you did to Elijah?
你是我的家人
You're my family.
况且，谁能比他深爱的女孩
Besides,
who better to spy on Marcel
更适合监视他呢？
than the girl he so clearly loves?
你可以告诉我他所有的秘密
You can tell me all his secrets.
比如他是如何找到我们住处的
Like how did he find us here?
你有什么想法吗，妹妹？
Any idea about that, little sister?
我怎么会知道马赛尔
为什么会做这些事？
How should I know
why Marcel does what he does?
你以为我不知道你在法语区那些
You think I don't know
about your engineered run-ins
设计好的小把戏吗？
all over the Quarter?
我知道你私下跟他聊过
I know you've had private chats with him.
快告诉我他都跟你说了什么秘密
So, just tell me what secrets
he's confided to you.
他是不是想暗算我？
Is he plotting against me?
我可怜的哥哥，太多疑了
My poor brother, so paranoid.
马赛尔什么都不知道
Marcel knows nothing.
他没有想暗算你
He is not plotting against you.
他只是简单地认为跟你吵了一架
He simply thinks
you're in a quarrel,
想跟你和好
in need of making up.
也许我们会的
Perhaps we will.
毕竟你知道我一向很善于
After all, you know
I'm capable of forgiving those
原谅那些让我失望的人
只要他们认识到错误
who disappoint me
soon as they've seen
并且为此付出代价就可以
the error of their ways
and suffered for them.
你要好好记住啊
You'd do well to remember that.
你从没让我忘记过
You never let me forget.
你想跟我做交易
You want to make
a deal with me,
你必须有所付出才行
you got to offer me something.
我已经知道那个叫海莉的狼女了
I already know about
Hayley the werewolf girl.
你还知道什么吗？
What else you got?
如果我告诉你那个狼女
What if I told you
that werewolf girl
正怀着克劳斯的孩子呢？
is carrying Klaus' child?
而且如果那个孩子出生
And if that baby is born...
就意味着吸血鬼种族的终结？
...it'll mean the end
of the vampire species?
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）